(Sheldon:)- He's a famous physicist...
- Yeah.
l know. He's the wheelchair dude
who invented time.
(Sheldon:)Close enough.
(Penny:)Why doesn't Howard
just introduce you to the guy?
(Sheldon:)Because he's punishing me
for being a, quote, "condescending jerk."
(Sheldon:)You don't think I'm condescending,
do you?
- Well...
- Oh, I'm sorry.
(Sheldon:)- Condescending means...
- l know what it means!
(Penny:)And, yes, you love correcting people
and putting them down.
(Sheldon:)Au contraire, when I correct people,
l am raising them up.
(Sheldon:)You should know.
l do it for you more than anyone.
(Penny:)Come on, you do it to feel superior.
l see that twinkle when someone
says "who" instead of "whom"...
(Penny:)...or thinks the moon is a planet.
(Sheldon:)Or Don Quixote is a book
about a donkey named Hotay.
See? There it is. There's that twinkle.
(Sheldon:)Well, I can't help it.
That's an involuntary twinkle.